Your most terrifying nightmare and your most frightening
reality are about to meet on the streets.
Tales from the Hood is a horror, crime, thriller
film directed by Rusty Cundieff.
A strange mortician tells four horrific tales to three drug
dealers that he traps in their local funeral parlor.
Mr. Simms (segment "Welcome to My Mortuary"), played by Clarence Williams III.
Stack (segment "Welcome to My Mortuary"), played by Joe Torry.
Ball (segment "Welcome to My Mortuary"), played by De'Aundre Bonds.
Bulldog (segment "Welcome to My Mortuary"), played by Samuel Monroe Jr..
Strom (segment "Rogue Cop Revelation"), played by Wings Hauser.
Martin Moorehouse (segment "Rogue Cop Revelation"), played by Tom Wright.
Tales from the Hood is a 1995 American black horror anthology film directed by Rusty Cundieff (who also wrote the film with Darin Scott) and starring Corbin
Bernsen, Rosalind Cash, Rusty Cundieff, David Alan Grier, Anthony Griffith, Wings Hauser, Paula Jai Parker, Joe Torry, and Clarence Williams III.
The film presents four short urban-themed horror stories based on problems that affect the
African-American community: police corruption, domestic abuse, racism, and gang violence.
These are presented within a frame story of three drug dealers buying some
"found" drugs from an eccentric and story-prone funeral director.
The film was met with mixed reviews upon release but
has since gained a cult following.
The film explores themes of prison, child abuse,
police brutality, ku klux klan, ghetto.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and emotional.